- No, absolutely not.
- It's not a big deal.
(Sheldon:)We have latex gloves.
(Leonard:)I don't care what the symptoms are.
My girlfriend is not gonna give you
a prostate exam.
- Hi, Sheldon.
- Good morning, Dr. Stephanie.
(Sheldon:)I trust Leonard satisfied you
sexually last night?
Oh, good God.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, we don't ask questions like that.
(Sheldon:)I heard you ask it over and over.
(Sheldon:)How is it inappropriate for me
to ask it once?
- He did very nicely.
- But see? She's not offended.
(Sheldon:)And now you finally have an answer.
- Out of coffee. Need coffee.
- Uh...
(Steph:)- Hello.
- Hi. Stephanie, right?
Mm-hm. And...? And you are?
(Penny:)I'm Penny. I live across the hall.
(Penny:)- Heard a lot about you.
- Really?
- Mm-hm. Ha, ha.
- I haven't heard a thing about you.